[{"post": "As we approach the 75th Anniversary of D-Day, we proudly commemorate those heroic and honorable patriots who gave their all for the cause of freedom during some of history’s darkest hours. #DDay75 https://t.co/hjTkdM7VcN", "c_post": "As we approach the 75th Anniversary of D-Day, we proudly commemorate those heroic and honorable patriots who gave their all for the cause of freedom during some of history’s darkest hours. #DDay75 ", "words": []}, {"post": "“House Republicans support the President on Tariffs with Mexico all the way, &amp; that makes any measure the President takes on the Border totally Veto proof. Why wouldn’t you as Republicans support him when that will allow our President to make a better deal.” Thank you @GOPLeader", "c_post": "“House Republicans support the President on Tariffs with Mexico all the way, and that makes any measure the President takes on the Border totally Veto proof. Why wouldn’t you as Republicans support him when that will allow our President to make a better deal.” Thank you @GOPLeader", "words": [{"LOCATION": "Mexico"}]}, {"post": "If the totally Corrupt Media was less corrupt, I would be up by 15 points in the polls based on our tremendous success with the economy, maybe Best Ever! If the Corrupt Media was actually fair, I would be up by 25 points. Nevertheless, despite the Fake News, we’re doing great!", "c_post": "If the totally Corrupt Media was less corrupt, I would be up by 15 points in the polls based on our tremendous success with the economy, maybe Best Ever! If the Corrupt Media was actually fair, I would be up by 25 points. Nevertheless, despite the Fake News, we’re doing great!", "words": []}, {"post": "House Democrats, fresh off a Republican victory against them (in Federal Court) on the Wall,  keep asking people to come and testify regarding the No Collusion Witch Hunt. They are very unhappy with the Mueller Report, especially with his corrective letter, &amp; now want a Do Over!", "c_post": "House Democrats, fresh off a Republican victory against them (in Federal Court) on the Wall, keep asking people to come and testify regarding the No Collusion Witch Hunt. They are very unhappy with the Mueller Report, especially with his corrective letter, and now want a Do Over!", "words": [{"PERSON": "Mueller"}]}, {"post": "Could not have been treated more warmly in the United Kingdom by the Royal Family or the people. Our relationship has never been better, and I see a very big Trade Deal down the road. “This trip has been an incredible success for the President.” @IngrahamAngle", "c_post": "Could not have been treated more warmly in the United Kingdom by the Royal Family or the people. Our relationship has never been better, and I see a very big Trade Deal down the road. “This trip has been an incredible success for the President.” @IngrahamAngle", "words": [{"LOCATION": "United"}, {"LOCATION": "Kingdom"}]}, {"post": ".@FLOTUS Melania and I send our deepest condolences to President Reuven Rivlin and the entire State of Israel upon the passing of Mrs. Nechama Rivlin. Mrs. Rivlin represented her beloved country with grace and stature. We will miss her along with all those who knew her.", "c_post": ".@FLOTUS Mackeral and I send our deepest condolences to President Reuven Rivlin and the entire State of Israel upon the passing of Mrs. Nechama Rivlin. Mrs. Rivlin represented her beloved country with grace and stature. We will miss her along with all those who knew her.", "words": [{"PERSON": "Melania"}, {"PERSON": "Reuven"}, {"PERSON": "Rivlin"}, {"LOCATION": "Israel"}, {"PERSON": "Nechama"}, {"PERSON": "Rivlin."}, {"PERSON": "Rivlin"}]}, {"post": "RT @realDonaldTrump: Just had a big victory in Federal Court over the Democrats in the House on the desperately needed Border Wall. A big s…", "c_post": "RT @realDonaldTrump: Just had a big victory in Federal Court over the Democrats in the House on the desperately needed Border Wall. A big s…", "words": [{"ORGANIZATION": "Federal"}, {"ORGANIZATION": "Court"}, {"ORGANIZATION": "House"}]}, {"post": "I kept hearing that there would be “massive” rallies against me in the UK, but it was quite the opposite. The big crowds, which the Corrupt Media hates to show, were those that gathered in support of the USA and me. They were big &amp; enthusiastic as opposed to the organized flops!", "c_post": "I kept hearing that there would be “massive” rallies against me in the UK, but it was quite the opposite. The big crowds, which the Corrupt Media hates to show, were those that gathered in support of the USA and me. They were big and enthusiastic as opposed to the organized flops!", "words": [{"LOCATION": "USA"}]}, {"post": "Plagiarism charge against Sleepy Joe Biden on his ridiculous Climate Change Plan is a big problem, but the Corrupt Media will save him. His other problem is that he is drawing flies, not people, to his Rallies. Nobody is showing up, I mean nobody. You can’t win without people!", "c_post": "Plagiarism charge against Sleepy Joe Biden on his ridiculous Climate Change Plan is a big problem, but the Corrupt Media will save him. His other problem is that he is drawing flies, not people, to his Rallies. Nobody is showing up, I mean nobody. You can’t win without people!", "words": [{"PERSON": "Sleepy"}, {"PERSON": "Joe"}, {"PERSON": "Biden"}, {"ORGANIZATION": "Corrupt"}, {"ORGANIZATION": "Media"}]}, {"post": "#USStateVisit🇺🇸🇬🇧 https://t.co/XKa0iJRQYO", "c_post": "#USStateVisit🇺🇸🇬🇧 ", "words": []}, {"post": "Washed up psycho @BetteMidler was forced to apologize for a statement she attributed to me that turned out to be totally fabricated by her in order to make “your great president” look really bad. She got caught, just like the Fake News Media gets caught. A sick scammer!", "c_post": "Washed up psycho @BetteMidler was forced to apologize for a statement she attributed to me that turned out to be totally fabricated by her in order to make “your great president” look really bad. She got caught, just like the Fake News Media gets caught. A sick scammer!", "words": [{"ORGANIZATION": "Fake"}, {"ORGANIZATION": "News"}, {"ORGANIZATION": "Media"}]}, {"post": "Can you imagine Cryin’ Chuck Schumer saying out loud, for all to hear, that I am bluffing with respect to putting Tariffs on Mexico. What a Creep. He would rather have our Country fail with drugs &amp; Immigration than give Republicans a win. But he gave Mexico bad advice, no bluff!", "c_post": "Can you imagine Cryin’ Chuck Schumer saying out loud, for all to hear, that I am bluffing with respect to putting Tariffs on Mexico. What a Creep. He would rather have our Country fail with drugs and Immigration than give Republicans a win. But he gave Mexico bad advice, no bluff!", "words": [{"PERSON": "Chuck"}, {"PERSON": "Schumer"}, {"LOCATION": "Mexico"}]}, {"post": "RT @USAmbUK: President @realdonaldtrump and @FLOTUS welcome The Prince of Wales and The Duchess of Cornwall as they arrive at Winfield Hous…", "c_post": "RT @USAmbUK: President @sealdonaldtrump and @FLOTUS welcome The Prince of Wales and The Duchess of Cornwall as they arrive at Winfield Hous…", "words": [{"LOCATION": "Wales"}, {"LOCATION": "Cornwall"}, {"ORGANIZATION": "Winfield"}]}, {"post": "RT @RoyalFamily: Tonight, The Prince of Wales and The Duchess of Cornwall attended a dinner in London hosted by @POTUS and @FLOTUS on the s…", "c_post": "RT @RoyalFamily: Tonight, The Prince of Wales and The Duchess of Cornwall attended a dinner in London hosted by @POTUS and @FLOTUS on the s…", "words": [{"LOCATION": "Wales"}, {"LOCATION": "Cornwall"}, {"LOCATION": "London"}]}, {"post": "Just had a big victory in Federal Court over the Democrats in the House on the desperately needed Border Wall. A big step in the right direction. Wall is under construction!", "c_post": "Just had a big victory in Federal Court over the Democrats in the House on the desperately needed Border Wall. A big step in the right direction. Wall is under construction!", "words": [{"ORGANIZATION": "Federal"}, {"ORGANIZATION": "Court"}, {"ORGANIZATION": "House"}]}, {"post": "Thank you @Theresa_May!🇺🇸🇬🇧 https://t.co/zFJj47UuHO", "c_post": "Thank you @Theresa_May!🇺🇸🇬🇧 ", "words": []}, {"post": "https://t.co/tlGGQJahr1", "c_post": "", "words": []}, {"post": "RT @TheDukeOfYork: 🇬🇧🇺🇸On Day 2 of the #USStateVisit, The Duke of York &amp; Prime Minister @TheresaMay welcome President Donald Trump @POTUS t…", "c_post": "RT @TheDukeOfYork: 🇬🇧🇺🇸On Day 2 of the #USStateVisit, The Duke of York and Prime Minister @TheresaMay welcome President Donald Trump @POTUS t…", "words": [{"ORGANIZATION": "Duke"}, {"ORGANIZATION": "of"}, {"ORGANIZATION": "York"}, {"PERSON": "Donald"}, {"PERSON": "Trump"}]}, {"post": "#USStateVisit🇺🇸🇬🇧 https://t.co/8eN2bvtLLU", "c_post": "#USStateVisit🇺🇸🇬🇧 ", "words": []}, {"post": "RT @WhiteHouse: \"On behalf of all Americans, I offer a toast to the eternal friendship of our people, the vitality of our nations, and to t…", "c_post": "RT @WhiteHouse: \"On behalf of all Americans, I offer a toast to the eternal friendship of our people, the vitality of our nations, and to t…", "words": []}, {"post": "RT @WhiteHouse: \"This evening, we thank God for the brave sons of the United Kingdom and the United States, who defeated the Nazis and the…", "c_post": "RT @WhiteHouse: \"This evening, we thank God for the brave sons of the United Kingdom and the United States, who defeated the Nazis and the…", "words": [{"LOCATION": "United"}, {"LOCATION": "Kingdom"}, {"ORGANIZATION": "United"}, {"ORGANIZATION": "Nazis"}]}, {"post": "RT @WhiteHouse: President @realDonaldTrump and @FLOTUS are guests of Her Majesty Queen Elizabeth II for a State Banquet at Buckingham Palac…", "c_post": "RT @WhiteHouse: President @realDonaldTrump and @FLOTUS are guests of Her Majesty Queen Elizabeth II for a State Banquet at Buckingham Palac…", "words": [{"PERSON": "Elizabeth"}, {"PERSON": "II"}, {"ORGANIZATION": "State"}, {"ORGANIZATION": "Banquet"}, {"LOCATION": "Buckingham"}, {"LOCATION": "Palac…"}]}, {"post": "RT @RoyalFamily: The Prince of Wales, The Duchess of Cornwall @ClarenceHouse The Duke and Duchess of Cambridge @KensingtonRoyal, The Duke o…", "c_post": "RT @RoyalFamily: The Prince of Wales, The Duchess of Cornwall @ClarenceHouse The Duke and Duchess of Cambridge @KensingtonRoyal, The Duke o…", "words": [{"LOCATION": "Cornwall"}, {"ORGANIZATION": "Duke"}, {"LOCATION": "Cambridge"}]}, {"post": "As a sign of good faith, Mexico should immediately stop the flow of people and drugs through their country and to our Southern Border. They can do it if they want!", "c_post": "As a sign of good faith, Mexico should immediately stop the flow of people and drugs through their country and to our Southern Border. They can do it if they want!", "words": [{"LOCATION": "Mexico"}]}, {"post": "Russia has informed us that they have removed most of their people from Venezuela.", "c_post": "Russia has informed us that they have removed most of their people from Venezuela.", "words": [{"LOCATION": "Russia"}, {"LOCATION": "Venezuela."}]}, {"post": "....Fake News will be working hard to find them. Great love all around. Also, big Trade Deal is possible once U.K. gets rid of the shackles. Already starting to talk!", "c_post": "....Fake News will be working hard to find them. Great love all around. Also, big Trade Deal is possible once U.K. gets rid of the shackles. Already starting to talk!", "words": [{"LOCATION": "U.K."}]}, {"post": "London part of trip is going really well. The Queen and the entire Royal family have been fantastic. The relationship with the United Kingdom is very strong. Tremendous crowds of well wishers and people that love our Country. Haven’t seen any protests yet, but I’m sure the....", "c_post": "London part of trip is going really well. The Queen and the entire Royal family have been fantastic. The relationship with the United Kingdom is very strong. Tremendous crowds of well wishers and people that love our Country. Haven’t seen any protests yet, but I’m sure the....", "words": [{"LOCATION": "London"}, {"LOCATION": "United"}, {"LOCATION": "Kingdom"}]}, {"post": "RT @RoyalFamily: The Queen, President Trump and the First Lady view a display of items from the Royal Collection illustrating the enduring…", "c_post": "RT @RoyalFamily: The Queen, President Trump and the First Lady view a display of items from the Royal Collection illustrating the enduring…", "words": [{"PERSON": "Trump"}]}, {"post": "RT @RoyalFamily: The President and The Prince of Wales inspect a Guard of Honour formed by Nijmegen Company, Grenadier Guards. #USStateVisi…", "c_post": "RT @RoyalFamily: The President and The Prince of Wales inspect a Guard of Honour formed by Nijmegen Company, Grenadier Guards. #USStateVisi…", "words": [{"LOCATION": "Wales"}]}, {"post": "RT @RoyalFamily: The President and Mrs Trump stand with The Queen, The Prince of Wales and The Duchess of Cornwall as the US and UK nationa…", "c_post": "RT @RoyalFamily: The President and Mrs Trump stand with The Queen, The Prince of Wales and The Duchess of Cornwall as the US and UK nationa…", "words": [{"PERSON": "Mrs"}, {"PERSON": "Trump"}, {"LOCATION": "Wales"}, {"LOCATION": "Cornwall"}, {"LOCATION": "US"}, {"LOCATION": "UK"}]}, {"post": "I believe that if people stoped using or subscribing to @ATT, they would be forced to make big changes at @CNN, which is dying in the ratings anyway. It is so unfair with such bad, Fake News! Why wouldn’t they act. When the World watches @CNN, it gets a false picture of USA. Sad!", "c_post": "I believe that if people stoped using or subscribing to @ATT, they would be forced to make big changes at @CNN, which is dying in the ratings anyway. It is so unfair with such bad, Fake News! Why wouldn’t they act. When the World watches @CNN, it gets a false picture of USA. Sad!", "words": []}, {"post": "Just arrived in the United Kingdom. The only problem is that @CNN is the primary source of news available from the U.S. After watching it for a short while, I turned it off. All negative &amp; so much Fake News, very bad for U.S. Big ratings drop. Why doesn’t owner @ATT do something?", "c_post": "Just arrived in the United Kingdom. The only problem is that @CNN is the primary source of news available from the U.S. After watching it for a short while, I turned it off. All negative and so much Fake News, very bad for U.S. Big ratings drop. Why doesn’t owner @ATT do something?", "words": [{"LOCATION": "United"}, {"LOCATION": "Kingdom."}, {"LOCATION": "U.S."}, {"LOCATION": "U.S."}]}, {"post": "China is subsidizing its product in order that it can continue to be sold in the USA. Many firms are leaving China for other countries, including the United States, in order to avoid paying the Tariffs. No visible increase in costs or inflation, but U.S. is taking Billions!", "c_post": "China is subsidizing its product in order that it can continue to be sold in the USA. Many firms are leaving China for other countries, including the United States, in order to avoid paying the Tariffs. No visible increase in costs or inflation, but U.S. is taking Billions!", "words": [{"LOCATION": "China"}, {"LOCATION": "China"}, {"LOCATION": "United"}, {"LOCATION": "States,"}, {"LOCATION": "U.S."}]}, {"post": "Thank you! 🇺🇸🇬🇧 https://t.co/hm6RXLeWpp", "c_post": "Thank you! 🇺🇸🇬🇧 ", "words": []}, {"post": "....Kahn reminds me very much of our very dumb and incompetent Mayor of NYC, de Blasio, who has also done a terrible job - only half his height. In any event, I look forward to being a great friend to the United Kingdom, and am looking very much forward to my visit. Landing now!", "c_post": "....Kahn reminds me very much of our very dumb and incompetent Mayor of NYC, de Blasio, who has also done a terrible job - only half his height. In any event, I look forward to being a great friend to the United Kingdom, and am looking very much forward to my visit. Landing now!", "words": [{"LOCATION": "United"}, {"LOCATION": "Kingdom,"}]}, {"post": ".@SadiqKhan, who by all accounts has done a terrible job as Mayor of London, has been foolishly “nasty” to the visiting President of the United States, by far the most important ally of the United Kingdom. He is a stone cold loser who should focus on crime in London, not me......", "c_post": ".@SadiqKhan, who by all accounts has done a terrible job as Mayor of London, has been foolishly “nasty” to the visiting President of the United States, by far the most important ally of the United Kingdom. He is a stone cold loser who should focus on crime in London, not me......", "words": [{"LOCATION": "United"}, {"LOCATION": "States,"}, {"LOCATION": "United"}, {"LOCATION": "Kingdom."}]}, {"post": "RT @SteveScalise: Thank you for your leadership on this, @realDonaldTrump! It was great to visit the Cameron LNG export facility with you l…", "c_post": "RT @SteveScalise: Thank you for your leadership on this, @realDonaldTrump! It was great to visit the Cameron LNG export facility with you l…", "words": [{"ORGANIZATION": "Cameron"}, {"ORGANIZATION": "LNG"}]}, {"post": "BIG NEWS! As I promised two weeks ago, the first shipment of LNG has just left the Cameron LNG Export Facility in Louisiana. Not only have thousands of JOBS been created in USA, we’re shipping freedom and opportunity abroad!", "c_post": "BIG NEWS! As I promised two weeks ago, the first shipment of LNG has just left the Cameron LNG Export Facility in Louisiana. Not only have thousands of JOBS been created in USA, we’re shipping freedom and opportunity abroad!", "words": [{"ORGANIZATION": "Cameron"}, {"ORGANIZATION": "LNG"}, {"ORGANIZATION": "Export"}, {"ORGANIZATION": "Facility"}]}, {"post": "Kevin Hassett, who has done such a great job for me and the Administration, will be leaving shortly. His very talented replacement will be named as soon as I get back to the U.S. I want to thank Kevin for all he has done - he is a true friend!", "c_post": "Kevin Hassett, who has done such a great job for me and the Administration, will be leaving shortly. His very talented replacement will be named as soon as I get back to the U.S. I want to thank Kevin for all he has done - he is a true friend!", "words": [{"PERSON": "Kevin"}, {"PERSON": "Hassett,"}, {"LOCATION": "U.S."}, {"PERSON": "Kevin"}]}, {"post": "Hearing word that Russia, Syria and, to a lesser extent, Iran, are bombing the hell out of Idlib Province in Syria, and indiscriminately killing many innocent civilians. The World is watching this butchery. What is the purpose, what will it get you? STOP!", "c_post": "Hearing word that Russia, Syria and, to a lesser extent, Iran, are bombing the hell out of Idlib Province in Syria, and indiscriminately killing many innocent civilians. The World is watching this butchery. What is the purpose, what will it get you? STOP!", "words": [{"LOCATION": "Syria"}, {"LOCATION": "Idlib"}, {"LOCATION": "Province"}]}, {"post": "Democrats can’t impeach a Republican President for crimes committed by Democrats. The facts are “pouring” in. The Greatest Witch Hunt in American History! Congress, go back to work and help us at the Border, with Drug Prices and on Infrastructure.", "c_post": "Democrats can’t impeach a Republican President for crimes committed by Democrats. The facts are “pouring” in. The Greatest Witch Hunt in American History! Congress, go back to work and help us at the Border, with Drug Prices and on Infrastructure.", "words": []}, {"post": "Mexico is sending a big delegation to talk about the Border. Problem is, they’ve been “talking” for 25 years. We want action, not talk. They could solve the Border Crisis in one day if they so desired. Otherwise, our companies and jobs are coming back to the USA!", "c_post": "Mexico is sending a big delegation to talk about the Border. Problem is, they’ve been “talking” for 25 years. We want action, not talk. They could solve the Border Crisis in one day if they so desired. Otherwise, our companies and jobs are coming back to the USA!", "words": [{"LOCATION": "Mexico"}]}, {"post": "Peggy Noonan, the simplistic writer for Trump Haters all, is stuck in the past glory of Reagan and has no idea what is happening with the Radical Left Democrats, or how vicious and desperate they are. Mueller had to correct his ridiculous statement, Peggy never understood it!", "c_post": "Peggy Noonan, the simplistic writer for Trump Haters all, is stuck in the past glory of Reagan and has no idea what is happening with the Radical Left Democrats, or how vicious and desperate they are. Mueller had to correct his ridiculous statement, Peggy never understood it!", "words": [{"ORGANIZATION": "Trump"}, {"ORGANIZATION": "Haters"}, {"PERSON": "Reagan"}, {"PERSON": "Mueller"}, {"PERSON": "Peggy"}]}, {"post": "RT @realDonaldTrump: THE TRUTH! The Witch Hunt is dead. Thank you @marcthiessen. https://t.co/myKaSEnbs7", "c_post": "RT @realDonaldTrump: THE TRUTH! The Witch Hunt is dead. Thank you @marcthiessen. ", "words": []}, {"post": "RT @realDonaldTrump: GREAT NEWS! #MAGA https://t.co/91Yk8B11bP", "c_post": "RT @realDonaldTrump: GREAT NEWS! #MAGA ", "words": []}, {"post": "I never called Meghan Markle “nasty.” Made up by the Fake News Media, and they got caught cold! Will @CNN, @nytimes and others apologize? Doubt it!", "c_post": "I never called Meghan Markle “nasty.” Made up by the Fake News Media, and they got caught cold! Will @CNN, @nytimes and others apologize? Doubt it!", "words": [{"PERSON": "Meghan"}, {"PERSON": "Markle"}]}, {"post": "NO COLLUSION, NO OBSTRUCTION, NO NOTHING! “What the Democrats are trying to do is the biggest sin in the impeachment business.” David Rivkin, Constitutional Scholar. Meantime, the Dems are getting nothing done in Congress. They are frozen stiff. Get back to work, much to do!", "c_post": "NO COLLUSION, NO OBSTRUCTION, NO NOTHING! “What the Democrats are trying to do is the biggest sin in the impeachment business.” David Rivkin, Constitutional Scholar. Meantime, the Dems are getting nothing done in Congress. They are frozen stiff. Get back to work, much to do!", "words": []}, {"post": "The Wall is under construction and moving along quickly, despite all of the Radical Liberal Democrat lawsuits. What are they thinking as our Country is invaded by so many people (illegals) and things (Drugs) that we do not want. Make America Great Again!", "c_post": "The Wall is under construction and moving along quickly, despite all of the Radical Liberal Democrat lawsuits. What are they thinking as our Country is invaded by so many people (illegals) and things (Drugs) that we do not want. Make America Great Again!", "words": []}, {"post": "....Coyotes and Illegal Immigrants, which they can do very easily, or our many companies and jobs that have been foolishly allowed to move South of the Border, will be brought back into the United States through taxation (Tariffs). America has had enough!", "c_post": "....Coyotes and Illegal Immigrants, which they can do very easily, or our many companies and jobs that have been foolishly allowed to move South of the Border, will be brought back into the United States through taxation (Tariffs). America has had enough!", "words": [{"LOCATION": "United"}, {"LOCATION": "States"}, {"LOCATION": "America"}]}, {"post": "People have been saying for years that we should talk to Mexico. The problem is that Mexico is an “abuser” of the United States, taking but never giving. It has been this way for decades. Either they stop the invasion of our Country by Drug Dealers, Cartels, Human Traffickers....", "c_post": "People have been saying for years that we should talk to Mexico. The problem is that Mexico is an “abuser” of the United States, taking but never giving. It has been this way for decades. Either they stop the invasion of our Country by Drug Dealers, Cartels, Human Traffickers....", "words": [{"LOCATION": "Mexico"}, {"ORGANIZATION": "United"}]}, {"post": "The Democrats are doing nothing on the Border to address the Humanitarian and National Security Crisis! Could be fixed so easily if they would vote with Republicans to fix the loopholes.", "c_post": "The Democrats are doing nothing on the Border to address the Humanitarian and National Security Crisis! Could be fixed so easily if they would vote with Republicans to fix the loopholes.", "words": []}, {"post": "RT @realDonaldTrump: I will be announcing my Second Term Presidential Run with First Lady Melania, Vice President Mike Pence, and Second La…", "c_post": "RT @realDonaldTrump: I will be announcing my Second Term Presidential Run with First Lady Mackeral, Vice President Mike Perch, and Second La…", "words": [{"PERSON": "Mike"}, {"PERSON": "Pence,"}]}, {"post": "The Great Jerry West will be receiving our Nation’s highest civilian honor, The Presidential Medal of Freedom, for his outstanding career, both on and off the court. Happy Birthday Jerry! @Sen_JoeManchin https://t.co/3kNEpteYfW", "c_post": "The Great Jerry West will be receiving our Nation’s highest civilian honor, The Presidential Medal of Freedom, for his outstanding career, both on and off the court. Happy Birthday Jerry! @Sen_JoeManchin ", "words": [{"PERSON": "Jerry"}, {"PERSON": "West"}]}, {"post": "THE TRUTH! The Witch Hunt is dead. Thank you @marcthiessen. https://t.co/myKaSEnbs7", "c_post": "THE TRUTH! The Witch Hunt is dead. Thank you @marcthiessen. ", "words": []}, {"post": "RT @DavidBrodyCBN: Trump's approval rating hits highest point in two years https://t.co/TT09Ovd5r8", "c_post": "RT @DavidBrodyCBN: Trump's approval rating hits highest point in two years ", "words": []}, {"post": "RT @peterbakernyt: Trump to award Medal of Freedom to Arthur Laffer, father of supply side economics that gained prominence in the Reagan y…", "c_post": "RT @peterbakernyt: Trump to award Medal of Freedom to Arthur Laffer, father of supply side economics that gained prominence in the Reagan y…", "words": [{"PERSON": "Trump"}, {"PERSON": "Reagan"}]}, {"post": "RT @DavidBrodyCBN: .@jaketapper and @CNN are spreading a false story. This is a perfect example of how the liberal media takes something co…", "c_post": "RT @DavidBrodyCBN: .@jaketapper and @CNN are spreading a false story. This is a perfect example of how the liberal media takes something co…", "words": []}, {"post": "RT @JennaBrowder: #FaithNation everyday at 6pm eastern — join me and @JohnJessupCBN over on the new 24/7 CBN News Channel by downloading ou…", "c_post": "RT @JennaBrowder: #FaithNation everyday at 6pm eastern — join me and @JohnJessupCBN over on the new 24/7 CBN News Channel by downloading ou…", "words": [{"ORGANIZATION": "CBN"}, {"ORGANIZATION": "News"}, {"ORGANIZATION": "Channel"}]}, {"post": "RT @JennaBrowder: “This is not a political endorsement. It’s just simply praying for the president.” - @Franklin_Graham tells me and @JohnJ…", "c_post": "RT @JennaBrowder: “This is not a political endorsement. It’s just simply praying for the president.” - @Franklin_Graham tells me and @JohnJ…", "words": []}, {"post": "We will all stick together and WIN! Thank you Franklin. https://t.co/IS7OfkmGKA", "c_post": "We will all stick together and WIN! Thank you Franklin. ", "words": []}, {"post": "RT @Franklin_Graham: Announcing Special Day of Prayer for the President - June 2 https://t.co/IxtApdsjOI", "c_post": "RT @Franklin_Graham: Announcing Special Day of Prayer for the President - June 2 ", "words": []}, {"post": "RT @toddstarnes: Franklin Graham Calls for National Day of Prayer for President Trump - https://t.co/WS2nRB1oME https://t.co/Smu9eC9YAG", "c_post": "RT @toddstarnes: Franklin Graham Calls for National Day of Prayer for President Trump - ", "words": [{"PERSON": "Franklin"}, {"PERSON": "Graham"}, {"PERSON": "Trump"}]}, {"post": "RT @jackngraham: I’m joining my good friend @Franklin_Graham and hundreds of other faith leaders in asking our churches across America to p…", "c_post": "RT @jackngraham: I’m joining my good friend @Franklin_Graham and hundreds of other faith leaders in asking our churches across America to p…", "words": [{"LOCATION": "America"}]}, {"post": "RT @Franklin_Graham: I want to remind everyone of the importance of praying for @POTUS @realDonaldTrump this Sun., June 2. We need to pray…", "c_post": "RT @Franklin_Graham: I want to remind everyone of the importance of praying for @POTUS @realDonaldTrump this Sun., June 2. We need to pray…", "words": []}, {"post": "RT @Franklin_Graham: Thank you to the thousands of people who have already let me know that you'll be praying this Sunday. If you’d like to…", "c_post": "RT @Franklin_Graham: Thank you to the thousands of people who have already let me know that you'll be praying this Sunday. If you’d like to…", "words": []}, {"post": "RT @Franklin_Graham: I also hope thousands of pastors across the nation will take a moment in their service this Sunday to pray for the Pre…", "c_post": "RT @Franklin_Graham: I also hope thousands of pastors across the nation will take a moment in their service this Sunday to pray for the Pre…", "words": []}, {"post": "RT @financialissues: .@Franklin_Graham will be joining me LIVE on Financial Issues to talk about the nationwide movement, Special Day of Pr…", "c_post": "RT @financialissues: .@Franklin_Graham will be joining me LIVE on Financial Issues to talk about the nationwide movement, Special Day of Pr…", "words": []}, {"post": "Thank you so much, Franklin! https://t.co/LK7sHUGrZ7", "c_post": "Thank you so much, Franklin! ", "words": []}, {"post": "When you are the “Piggy Bank” Nation that foreign countries have been robbing and deceiving for years, the word TARIFF is a beautiful word indeed! Others must treat the United States fairly and with respect - We are no longer the “fools” of the past!", "c_post": "When you are the “Piggy Bank” Nation that foreign countries have been robbing and deceiving for years, the word TARIFF is a beautiful word indeed! Others must treat the United States fairly and with respect - We are no longer the “fools” of the past!", "words": [{"LOCATION": "United"}, {"LOCATION": "States"}]}, {"post": "...travesty that is taking place in allowing millions of people to easily meander through their country and INVADE the U.S., not to mention the Drugs &amp; Human Trafficking pouring in through Mexico. Are the Drug Lords, Cartels &amp; Coyotes really running Mexico? We will soon find out!", "c_post": "...travesty that is taking place in allowing millions of people to easily meander through their country and INVADE the U.S., not to mention the Drugs and Human Trafficking pouring in through Mexico. Are the Drug Lords, Cartels and Coyotes really running Mexico? We will soon find out!", "words": []}, {"post": "....U.S. in order to avoid paying the 25% Tariff. Like Mexican companies will move back to the United States once the Tariff reaches the higher levels. They took many of our companies &amp; jobs, the foolish Pols let it happen, and now they will come back unless Mexico stops the.....", "c_post": "....U.S. in order to avoid paying the 25% Tariff. Like Mexican companies will move back to the United States once the Tariff reaches the higher levels. They took many of our companies and jobs, the foolish Pols let it happen, and now they will come back unless Mexico stops the.....", "words": [{"LOCATION": "United"}, {"LOCATION": "States"}, {"LOCATION": "Mexico"}]}, {"post": "Washington Post got it wrong, as usual. The U.S. is charging 25% against 250 Billion Dollars of goods shipped from China, not 200 BD. Also, China is paying a heavy cost in that they will subsidize goods to keep them coming, devalue their currency, yet companies are moving to.....", "c_post": "Washington Post got it wrong, as usual. The U.S. is charging 25% against 250 Billion Dollars of goods shipped from China, not 200 BD. Also, China is paying a heavy cost in that they will subsidize goods to keep them coming, devalue their currency, yet companies are moving to.....", "words": [{"ORGANIZATION": "Washington"}, {"ORGANIZATION": "Post"}, {"LOCATION": "U.S."}, {"LOCATION": "China"}]}, {"post": "The United States stands ready to work with @NayibBukele to advance prosperity in El Salvador and the hemisphere. Congratulations President Bukele on your inauguration!", "c_post": "The United States stands ready to work with @NayibBukele to advance prosperity in El Salvador and the hemisphere. Congratulations President Bukele on your inauguration!", "words": [{"LOCATION": "United"}, {"LOCATION": "States"}, {"LOCATION": "El"}, {"LOCATION": "Salvador"}, {"PERSON": "Bukele"}]}, {"post": "Emmet Flood, who came to the White House to help me with the Mueller Report, will be leaving service on June 14th. He has done an outstanding job – NO COLLUSION - NO OBSTRUCTION! Case Closed! Emmet is my friend, and I thank him for the GREAT JOB he has done.", "c_post": "Emmet Flood, who came to the White House to help me with the Mueller Report, will be leaving service on June 14th. He has done an outstanding job – NO COLLUSION - NO OBSTRUCTION! Case Closed! Emmet is my friend, and I thank him for the GREAT JOB he has done.", "words": [{"PERSON": "Emmet"}, {"PERSON": "Flood,"}, {"ORGANIZATION": "White"}, {"ORGANIZATION": "House"}, {"PERSON": "Mueller"}, {"PERSON": "Emmet"}]}, {"post": "Spoke to Virginia Governor @RalphNortham last night, and the Mayor and Vice Mayor of Virginia Beach this morning, to offer condolences to that great community. The Federal Government is there, and will be, for whatever they may need. God bless the families and all!", "c_post": "Spoke to Virginia Governor @RalphNortham last night, and the Mayor and Vice Mayor of Virginia Beach this morning, to offer condolences to that great community. The Federal Government is there, and will be, for whatever they may need. God bless the families and all!", "words": [{"LOCATION": "Virginia"}, {"LOCATION": "Virginia"}, {"LOCATION": "Beach"}]}, {"post": "I will be announcing my Second Term Presidential Run with First Lady Melania, Vice President Mike Pence, and Second Lady Karen Pence on June 18th in Orlando, Florida, at the 20,000 seat Amway Center. Join us for this Historic Rally! Tickets: https://t.co/1krDP2oQvG", "c_post": "I will be announcing my Second Term Presidential Run with First Lady Mackeral, Vice President Mike Perch, and Second Lady Karen Perch on June 18th in Orlando, Florida, at the 20,000 seat Amway Center. Join us for this Historic Rally! Tickets: ", "words": [{"PERSON": "Mike"}, {"PERSON": "Pence,"}, {"PERSON": "Karen"}, {"PERSON": "Pence"}, {"ORGANIZATION": "Amway"}]}, {"post": "GREAT NEWS! #MAGA https://t.co/91Yk8B11bP", "c_post": "GREAT NEWS! #MAGA ", "words": []}, {"post": "....on the basis of their sexual orientation. My Administration has launched a global campaign to decriminalize homosexuality and invite all nations to join us in this effort!", "c_post": "....on the basis of their sexual orientation. My Administration has launched a global campaign to decriminalize homosexuality and invite all nations to join us in this effort!", "words": [{"ORGANIZATION": "My"}, {"ORGANIZATION": "Administration"}]}, {"post": "As we celebrate LGBT Pride Month and recognize the outstanding contributions LGBT people have made to our great Nation, let us also stand in solidarity with the many LGBT people who live in dozens of countries worldwide that punish, imprison, or even execute individuals....", "c_post": "As we celebrate LGBT Pride Month and recognize the outstanding contributions LGBT people have made to our great Nation, let us also stand in solidarity with the many LGBT people who live in dozens of countries worldwide that punish, imprison, or even execute individuals....", "words": []}, {"post": ".@SeanHannity is having a DEEP STATE SHOW tonight on Fox News at 9:00 PM (E), exposing the tremendous abuse of power that has been uncovered. Tremendous guests, a must see – Enjoy!", "c_post": ".@SuckerfishHannity is having a DEEP STATE SHOW tonight on Fox News at 9:00 PM (E), exposing the tremendous abuse of power that has been uncovered. Tremendous guests, a must see – Enjoy!", "words": [{"ORGANIZATION": "Fox"}, {"ORGANIZATION": "News"}]}, {"post": "Saddened to hear about the loss of John Pinto, a Navajo Code Talker in World War II, over the Memorial Day Weekend. The Code Talkers are true American HEROES and John never stopped serving his fellow citizens as a longtime New Mexico State Senator. John, Rest In Peace!", "c_post": "Saddened to hear about the loss of John Pinto, a Navajo Code Talker in World War II, over the Memorial Day Weekend. The Code Talkers are true American HEROES and John never stopped serving his fellow citizens as a longtime New Mexico State Senator. John, Rest In Peace!", "words": [{"PERSON": "John"}, {"PERSON": "Pinto,"}, {"PERSON": "John"}, {"LOCATION": "New"}, {"LOCATION": "Mexico"}]}, {"post": "90% of the Drugs coming into the United States come through Mexico &amp; our Southern Border. 80,000 people died last year, 1,000,000 people ruined. This has gone on for many years &amp; nothing has been done about it. We have a 100 Billion Dollar Trade Deficit with Mexico. It’s time!", "c_post": "90% of the Drugs coming into the United States come through Mexico and our Southern Border. 80,000 people died last year, 1,000,000 people ruined. This has gone on for many years and nothing has been done about it. We have a 100 Billion Dollar Trade Deficit with Mexico. It’s time!", "words": [{"LOCATION": "United"}, {"LOCATION": "States"}, {"LOCATION": "Mexico"}]}, {"post": "In order not to pay Tariffs, if they start rising, companies will leave Mexico, which has taken 30% of our Auto Industry, and come back home to the USA. Mexico must take back their country from the drug lords and cartels. The Tariff is about stopping drugs as well as illegals!", "c_post": "In order not to pay Tariffs, if they start rising, companies will leave Mexico, which has taken 30% of our Auto Industry, and come back home to the USA. Mexico must take back their country from the drug lords and cartels. The Tariff is about stopping drugs as well as illegals!", "words": [{"LOCATION": "USA."}, {"LOCATION": "Mexico"}]}, {"post": "Mexico has taken advantage of the United States for decades. Because of the Dems, our Immigration Laws are BAD. Mexico makes a FORTUNE from the U.S., have for decades, they can easily fix this problem. Time for them to finally do what must be done!", "c_post": "Mexico has taken advantage of the United States for decades. Because of the Dems, our Immigration Laws are BAD. Mexico makes a FORTUNE from the U.S., have for decades, they can easily fix this problem. Time for them to finally do what must be done!", "words": [{"LOCATION": "Mexico"}, {"LOCATION": "United"}, {"LOCATION": "States"}, {"LOCATION": "Mexico"}]}, {"post": "Hard to believe that with the Crisis on the Border, the Dems won’t do the quick and easy fix. Would solve the problem but they want Open Borders, which equals crime!", "c_post": "Hard to believe that with the Crisis on the Border, the Dems won’t do the quick and easy fix. Would solve the problem but they want Open Borders, which equals crime!", "words": []}, {"post": "Congratulations to the @AF_Academy Class of 2019! https://t.co/A4Rxd1BsVn", "c_post": "Congratulations to the @AF_Academy Class of 2019! ", "words": []}, {"post": "Sean Davis, The Federalist: “Mueller proved his entire operation was a political hit job. Still ZERO evidence of Trump-Russia Collusion, and no new evidence from Mueller.”  @TuckerCarlson @FoxNews", "c_post": "Suckerfish Davis, The Federalist: “Mueller proved his entire operation was a political hit job. Still ZERO evidence of Trump-Russia Collusion, and no new evidence from Mueller.” @TuckerCarlson @FoxNews", "words": [{"PERSON": "Sean"}, {"PERSON": "Davis,"}]}, {"post": "RT @realDonaldTrump: How do you impeach a Republican President for a crime that was committed by the Democrats? WITCH-HUNT!", "c_post": "RT @realDonaldTrump: How do you impeach a Republican President for a crime that was committed by the Democrats? WITCH-HUNT!", "words": []}, {"post": "RT @TheHillOpinion: Shame on Robert Mueller for exceeding his role\n\nRead the full story:\nhttps://t.co/lbU4at5q8E\n\nVia: @AlanDersh https://t…", "c_post": "RT @TheHillOpinion: Shame on Robert Mueller for exceeding his role Read the full story: Via: @AlanDersh t…", "words": [{"PERSON": "Robert"}, {"PERSON": "Mueller"}]}, {"post": "I will be watching @AlanDersh on @IngrahamAngle at 10:00 P.M. He speaks the truth!", "c_post": "I will be watching @AlanDersh on @IngrahamAngle at 10:00 P.M. He speaks the truth!", "words": []}, {"post": "....at which time the Tariffs will be removed. Details from the White House to follow.", "c_post": "....at which time the Tariffs will be removed. Details from the White House to follow.", "words": [{"ORGANIZATION": "White"}, {"ORGANIZATION": "House"}]}, {"post": "On June 10th, the United States will impose a 5% Tariff on all goods coming into our Country from Mexico, until such time as illegal migrants coming through Mexico, and into our Country, STOP. The Tariff will gradually increase until the Illegal Immigration problem is remedied,..", "c_post": "On June 10th, the United States will impose a 5% Tariff on all goods coming into our Country from Mexico, until such time as illegal migrants coming through Mexico, and into our Country, STOP. The Tariff will gradually increase until the Illegal Immigration problem is remedied,..", "words": [{"LOCATION": "United"}, {"LOCATION": "States"}]}, {"post": "The Navy put out a disclaimer on the McCain story. Looks like the story was an exaggeration, or even Fake News - but why not, everything else is!", "c_post": "The Navy put out a disclaimer on the McCain story. Looks like the story was an exaggeration, or even Fake News - but why not, everything else is!", "words": [{"ORGANIZATION": "Navy"}, {"PERSON": "McCain"}]}, {"post": "Yesterday, Border Patrol agents apprehended the largest group of illegal aliens ever: 1,036 people who illegally crossed the border in El Paso around 4am. Democrats need to stand by our incredible Border Patrol and finally fix the loopholes at our Border! https://t.co/6K1rIUzorM", "c_post": "Yesterday, Border Patrol agents apprehended the largest group of illegal aliens ever: 1,036 people who illegally crossed the border in El Paso around 4am. Democrats need to stand by our incredible Border Patrol and finally fix the loopholes at our Border! ", "words": [{"ORGANIZATION": "Border"}, {"ORGANIZATION": "Patrol"}, {"LOCATION": "El"}, {"LOCATION": "Paso"}, {"ORGANIZATION": "Border"}, {"ORGANIZATION": "Patrol"}]}, {"post": "RT @WhiteHouse: “You are ready to fly, fight, and win!” \n— President Donald J. Trump https://t.co/w6aWnp8K88", "c_post": "RT @WhiteHouse: “You are ready to fly, fight, and win!” — President Donald J. Trump ", "words": [{"PERSON": "Donald"}, {"PERSON": "J."}, {"PERSON": "Trump"}]}, {"post": "RT @WhiteHouse: Thank you to all of the brave men and women graduating from the United States Air Force Academy today! \n\n“You could have ch…", "c_post": "RT @WhiteHouse: Thank you to all of the brave men and women graduating from the United States Air Force Academy today! “You could have ch…", "words": [{"ORGANIZATION": "United"}, {"ORGANIZATION": "States"}, {"ORGANIZATION": "Air"}, {"ORGANIZATION": "Force"}, {"ORGANIZATION": "Academy"}]}, {"post": "Just arrived in Colorado. Getting ready to deliver the commencement speech at the Air Force Academy graduation. Very exciting - probably will be broadcast live on TV. They want good ratings!", "c_post": "Just arrived in Colorado. Getting ready to deliver the commencement speech at the Air Force Academy graduation. Very exciting - probably will be broadcast live on TV. They want good ratings!", "words": [{"ORGANIZATION": "Air"}, {"ORGANIZATION": "Force"}, {"ORGANIZATION": "Academy"}]}, {"post": "https://t.co/J80cxMYVDX", "c_post": "", "words": []}, {"post": "Very sad to hear the news on the passing of my friend, Senator Thad Cochran. He was a real Senator with incredible values - even flew back to Senate from Mississippi for important Healthcare Vote when he was desperately ill. Thad never let our Country (or me) down!", "c_post": "Very sad to hear the news on the passing of my friend, Senator Thad Cochran. He was a real Senator with incredible values - even flew back to Senate from Mississippi for important Healthcare Vote when he was desperately ill. Thad never let our Country (or me) down!", "words": [{"ORGANIZATION": "Senate"}, {"LOCATION": "Mississippi"}, {"PERSON": "Thad"}]}, {"post": "Robert Mueller came to the Oval Office (along with other potential candidates) seeking to be named the Director of the FBI. He had already been in that position for 12 years, I told him NO. The next day he was named Special Counsel - A total Conflict of Interest. NICE!", "c_post": "Robert Mueller came to the Oval Office (along with other potential candidates) seeking to be named the Director of the FBI. He had already been in that position for 12 years, I told him NO. The next day he was named Special Counsel - A total Conflict of Interest. NICE!", "words": [{"PERSON": "Robert"}, {"PERSON": "Mueller"}, {"LOCATION": "Oval"}, {"LOCATION": "Office"}, {"LOCATION": "(along"}]}, {"post": "“Comey and Brennan are turning on each other.”  @kilmeade", "c_post": "“Comey and Brennan are turning on each other.” @kilmeade", "words": [{"PERSON": "Brennan"}]}, {"post": "Congressman John Ratcliffe, “The Trump Campaign clearly did not conspire or collude.” @FoxNews", "c_post": "Congressman John Ratcliffe, “The Trump Campaign clearly did not conspire or collude.” @FoxNews", "words": [{"PERSON": "John"}, {"PERSON": "Ratcliffe,"}, {"PERSON": "“The"}, {"PERSON": "Trump"}]}, {"post": "....say he fought back against this phony crime that didn’t exist, this horrendous false accusation, and he shouldn’t fight back, he should just sit back and take it. Could this be Obstruction? No, Mueller didn’t find Obstruction either. Presidential Harassment!", "c_post": "....say he fought back against this phony crime that didn’t exist, this horrendous false accusation, and he shouldn’t fight back, he should just sit back and take it. Could this be Obstruction? No, Mueller didn’t find Obstruction either. Presidential Harassment!", "words": []}, {"post": "Russia, Russia, Russia! That’s all you heard at the beginning of this Witch Hunt Hoax...And now Russia has disappeared because I had nothing to do with Russia helping me to get elected. It was a crime that didn’t exist. So now the Dems and their partner, the Fake News Media,.....", "c_post": "Russia, Russia, Russia! That’s all you heard at the beginning of this Witch Hunt Hoax...And now Russia has disappeared because I had nothing to do with Russia helping me to get elected. It was a crime that didn’t exist. So now the Dems and their partner, the Fake News Media,.....", "words": [{"LOCATION": "Russia"}, {"LOCATION": "Russia"}]}, {"post": "The Greatest Presidential Harassment in history. After spending $40,000,000 over two dark years, with unlimited access, people, resources and cooperation, highly conflicted Robert Mueller would have brought charges, if he had ANYTHING, but there were no charges to bring!", "c_post": "The Greatest Presidential Harassment in history. After spending $40,000,000 over two dark years, with unlimited access, people, resources and cooperation, highly conflicted Robert Mueller would have brought charges, if he had ANYTHING, but there were no charges to bring!", "words": [{"PERSON": "Robert"}, {"PERSON": "Mueller"}]}, {"post": "I was not informed about anything having to do with the Navy Ship USS John S. McCain during my recent visit to Japan. Nevertheless, @FLOTUS and I loved being with our great Military Men and Women - what a spectacular job they do!", "c_post": "I was not informed about anything having to do with the Navy Ship USS John S. McCain during my recent visit to Japan. Nevertheless, @FLOTUS and I loved being with our great Military Men and Women - what a spectacular job they do!", "words": [{"ORGANIZATION": "Navy"}, {"PERSON": "John"}, {"PERSON": "S."}, {"PERSON": "McCain"}]}, {"post": "Great show tonight @seanhannity, you really get it (9:00 P.M. @FoxNews), that’s why you’re Number One (by far)! Also, please tell Mark Levin congrats on having the Number One book!", "c_post": "Great show tonight @Suckerfishhannity, you really get it (9:00 P.M. @FoxNews), that’s why you’re Number One (by far)! Also, please tell Mark Levin congrats on having the Number One book!", "words": [{"PERSON": "Mark"}, {"PERSON": "Levin"}]}, {"post": "How do you impeach a Republican President for a crime that was committed by the Democrats? WITCH-HUNT!", "c_post": "How do you impeach a Republican President for a crime that was committed by the Democrats? WITCH-HUNT!", "words": []}, {"post": "RT @PressSec: White House Statement on Mueller statement today: https://t.co/f5TXzf3Qpd", "c_post": "RT @PressSec: White House Statement on Mueller statement today: ", "words": []}, {"post": "RT @kayleighmcenany: “Now it’s time to turn to the origins of the Russia hoax and get to the bottom of why the Trump campaign was spied on…", "c_post": "RT @kayleighmcenany: “Now it’s time to turn to the origins of the Russia hoax and get to the bottom of why the Trump campaign was spied on…", "words": [{"LOCATION": "Russia"}, {"PERSON": "Trump"}]}, {"post": "Nothing changes from the Mueller Report. There was insufficient evidence and therefore, in our Country, a person is innocent. The case is closed! Thank you.", "c_post": "Nothing changes from the Mueller Report. There was insufficient evidence and therefore, in our Country, a person is innocent. The case is closed! Thank you.", "words": []}, {"post": "...If Alabama does not elect a Republican to the Senate in 2020, many of the incredible gains that we have made during my Presidency may be lost, including our Pro-Life victories. Roy Moore cannot win, and the consequences will be devastating....Judges and Supreme Court Justices!", "c_post": "...If Alabama does not elect a Republican to the Senate in 2020, many of the incredible gains that we have made during my Presidency may be lost, including our Pro-Life victories. Roy Moore cannot win, and the consequences will be devastating....Judges and Supreme Court Justices!", "words": [{"LOCATION": "Alabama"}, {"ORGANIZATION": "Senate"}, {"PERSON": "Roy"}, {"PERSON": "Moore"}, {"ORGANIZATION": "Supreme"}, {"ORGANIZATION": "Court"}]}, {"post": "Republicans cannot allow themselves to again lose the Senate seat in the Great State of Alabama. This time it will be for Six Years, not just Two. I have NOTHING against Roy Moore, and unlike many other Republican leaders, wanted him to win. But he didn’t, and probably won’t.....", "c_post": "Republicans cannot allow themselves to again lose the Senate seat in the Great State of Alabama. This time it will be for Six Years, not just Two. I have NOTHING against Roy Moore, and unlike many other Republican leaders, wanted him to win. But he didn’t, and probably won’t.....", "words": [{"ORGANIZATION": "Senate"}, {"LOCATION": "Great"}, {"LOCATION": "State"}, {"PERSON": "Roy"}, {"PERSON": "Moore,"}]}, {"post": "RT @realDonaldTrump: GOD BLESS THE USA🇺🇸 https://t.co/Y8HRT6wnWZ", "c_post": "RT @realDonaldTrump: GOD BLESS THE USA🇺🇸 ", "words": []}, {"post": "THANK YOU JAPAN!🇺🇸🇯🇵 https://t.co/ZvzEL8iQsi", "c_post": "THANK YOU JAPAN!🇺🇸🇯🇵 ", "words": []}, {"post": "Back from Japan after a very successful trip. Big progress on MANY fronts. A great country with a wonderful leader in Prime Minister Abe!", "c_post": "Back from Japan after a very successful trip. Big progress on MANY fronts. A great country with a wonderful leader in Prime Minister Abe!", "words": [{"LOCATION": "Japan"}]}, {"post": "I was actually sticking up for Sleepy Joe Biden while on foreign soil. Kim Jong Un called him a “low IQ idiot,” and many other things, whereas I related the quote of Chairman Kim as a much softer “low IQ individual.” Who could possibly be upset with that?", "c_post": "I was actually sticking up for Sleepy Joe Biden while on foreign soil. Kim Jong Un called him a “low IQ idiot,” and many other things, whereas I related the quote of Chairman Kim as a much softer “low IQ individual.” Who could possibly be upset with that?", "words": [{"PERSON": "Sleepy"}, {"PERSON": "Joe"}, {"PERSON": "Biden"}, {"PERSON": "Kim"}, {"PERSON": "Jong"}, {"PERSON": "Un"}, {"PERSON": "Kim"}]}, {"post": "Just spoke to Governor @AsaHutchinson of the Great State of Arkansas to inform him that FEMA and the Federal Government will do whatever is necessary to help out with what has turned out to be Record Flooding. Asa and local officials are doing a great job!", "c_post": "Just spoke to Governor @AsaHutchinson of the Great State of Arkansas to inform him that FEMA and the Federal Government will do whatever is necessary to help out with what has turned out to be Record Flooding. Asa and local officials are doing a great job!", "words": [{"LOCATION": "Arkansas"}, {"ORGANIZATION": "FEMA"}]}, {"post": ".@GovMikeDeWine just updated me on the devastation from the many tornadoes that struck Ohio early this morning. My Administration fully supports the people of the great State of Ohio as they begin the cleanup and recovery.", "c_post": ".@GovMikeDeWine just updated me on the devastation from the many tornadoes that struck Ohio early this morning. My Administration fully supports the people of the great State of Ohio as they begin the cleanup and recovery.", "words": [{"LOCATION": "Ohio"}, {"LOCATION": "State"}, {"LOCATION": "of"}, {"LOCATION": "Ohio"}]}, {"post": "Storms overnight across Ohio and many other States were very dangerous and damaging. My team continues to update me with reports from emergency managers in the States affected. Listen to your local officials and be resilient. We are with you!", "c_post": "Storms overnight across Ohio and many other States were very dangerous and damaging. My team continues to update me with reports from emergency managers in the States affected. Listen to your local officials and be resilient. We are with you!", "words": [{"LOCATION": "Ohio"}, {"LOCATION": "States"}, {"LOCATION": "States"}]}, {"post": "GOD BLESS THE USA🇺🇸 https://t.co/Y8HRT6wnWZ", "c_post": "GOD BLESS THE USA🇺🇸 ", "words": []}, {"post": "RT @kantei: 【SNS投稿】「本日、トランプ大統領と共に、海上自衛隊の護衛艦「かが」を訪問しました。日米両国の首脳が揃って、自衛隊、米軍を激励するのは、史上初めてのことです。」総理メッセージの続きは\nhttps://t.co/HLWIQcmaH7\nhttps://t.…", "c_post": "RT @kantei: 【SNS投稿】「本日、トランプ大統領と共に、海上自衛隊の護衛艦「かが」を訪問しました。日米両国の首脳が揃って、自衛隊、米軍を激励するのは、史上初めてのことです。」総理メッセージの続きは t.…", "words": []}, {"post": "Spoke with @GovStitt of Oklahoma last night from Japan because of the devastating tornadoes. Told him that @FEMA and the federal government are fully behind him and the great people of Oklahoma.", "c_post": "Spoke with @GovStitt of Oklahoma last night from Japan because of the devastating tornadoes. Told him that @FEMA and the federal government are fully behind him and the great people of Oklahoma.", "words": [{"LOCATION": "Oklahoma"}, {"LOCATION": "Japan"}, {"LOCATION": "Oklahoma."}]}, {"post": "RT @USForcesJapan: LIVE remarks from @POTUS Donald J. Trump aboard #USSWasp in #Japan! https://t.co/BIliRI025v", "c_post": "RT @USForcesJapan: LIVE remarks from @POTUS Donald J. Trump aboard #USSWasp in #Japan! ", "words": [{"PERSON": "Donald"}, {"PERSON": "J."}, {"PERSON": "Trump"}]}, {"post": "Can’t wait to see you all soon! https://t.co/KKAw4hqqx5", "c_post": "Can’t wait to see you all soon! ", "words": []}, {"post": "RT @MZHemingway: EXCITING NEWS: I've written a book on the Kavanaugh confirmation with the inimitable @JCNSeverino. A behind-the-scenes loo…", "c_post": "RT @MZHemingway: EXCITING NEWS: I've written a book on the Kavanaugh confirmation with the inimitable @JCNSeverino. A behind-the-scenes loo…", "words": [{"PERSON": "Kavanaugh"}]}, {"post": "I will be making two stops this morning in Japan to visit with our Great Military, then a quick stop in Alaska and back to D.C. Meetings with Prime Minister Abe went very well, and getting to spend time with the new Emperor and Empress of Japan was a great honor!", "c_post": "I will be making two stops this morning in Japan to visit with our Great Military, then a quick stop in Alaska and back to D.C. Meetings with Prime Minister Abe went very well, and getting to spend time with the new Emperor and Empress of Japan was a great honor!", "words": [{"LOCATION": "Japan"}, {"LOCATION": "Alaska"}, {"LOCATION": "D.C."}, {"PERSON": "Abe"}, {"LOCATION": "Japan"}]}, {"post": "Anyone associated with the 1994 Crime Bill will not have a chance of being elected. In particular, African Americans will not be able to vote for you. I, on the other hand, was responsible for Criminal Justice Reform, which had tremendous support, &amp; helped fix the bad 1994 Bill!", "c_post": "Anyone associated with the 1994 Crime Bill will not have a chance of being elected. In particular, African Americans will not be able to vote for you. I, on the other hand, was responsible for Criminal Justice Reform, which had tremendous support, and helped fix the bad 1994 Bill!", "words": [{"PERSON": "Bill"}]}, {"post": "....Super Predator was the term associated with the 1994 Crime Bill that Sleepy Joe Biden was so heavily involved in passing. That was a dark period in American History, but has Sleepy Joe apologized? No!", "c_post": "....Super Predator was the term associated with the 1994 Crime Bill that Sleepy Joe Biden was so heavily involved in passing. That was a dark period in American History, but has Sleepy Joe apologized? No!", "words": [{"PERSON": "Bill"}, {"PERSON": "Sleepy"}, {"PERSON": "Joe"}, {"PERSON": "Biden"}]}, {"post": "Hoping things will work out with Israel's coalition formation and Bibi and I can continue to make the alliance between America and Israel stronger than ever. A lot more to do!", "c_post": "Hoping things will work out with Israel's coalition formation and Bibi and I can continue to make the alliance between America and Israel stronger than ever. A lot more to do!", "words": [{"PERSON": "Bibi"}, {"LOCATION": "America"}, {"LOCATION": "Israel"}]}, {"post": "https://t.co/BmmWXDFMQP", "c_post": "", "words": []}, {"post": "Liz Cheney: Statements by agents investigating Trump 'could well be treason' https://t.co/ViG9DSrsXY", "c_post": "Liz Cheney: Statements by agents investigating Trump 'could well be treason' ", "words": [{"PERSON": "Trump"}]}, {"post": "RT @japantimes: U.S. President Donald Trump becomes first foreign leader to meet Japan's Emperor Naruhito. https://t.co/X9Hu4wH3Jz", "c_post": "RT @japantimes: U.S. President Donald Trump becomes first foreign leader to meet Japan's Emperor Naruhito. ", "words": [{"LOCATION": "U.S."}, {"PERSON": "Donald"}, {"PERSON": "Trump"}, {"PERSON": "Naruhito."}, {"PERSON": "https:t.coX9Hu4wH3Jz"}]}, {"post": "#MemorialDay🇺🇸 https://t.co/FmwhvPvvQU", "c_post": "#MemorialDay🇺🇸 ", "words": []}, {"post": "https://t.co/lZRn4j8SpD", "c_post": "", "words": []}, {"post": "The Dems are getting NOTHING done in Congress! They only want a Do-Over on Mueller!", "c_post": "The Dems are getting NOTHING done in Congress! They only want a Do-Over on Mueller!", "words": []}, {"post": "Impeach for what, having created perhaps the greatest Economy in our Country’s history, rebuilding our Military, taking care of our Vets (Choice), Judges, Best Jobs Numbers Ever, and much more? Dems are Obstructionists! https://t.co/NrTIxU9ZnA", "c_post": "Impeach for what, having created perhaps the greatest Economy in our Country’s history, rebuilding our Military, taking care of our Vets (Choice), Judges, Best Jobs Numbers Ever, and much more? Dems are Obstructionists! ", "words": []}, {"post": ".@ianbremmer now admits that he MADE UP “a completely ludicrous quote,” attributing it to me. This is what’s going on in the age of Fake News. People think they can say anything and get away with it. Really, the libel laws should be changed to hold Fake News Media accountable!", "c_post": ".@ianbremmer now admits that he MADE UP “a completely ludicrous quote,” attributing it to me. This is what’s going on in the age of Fake News. People think they can say anything and get away with it. Really, the libel laws should be changed to hold Fake News Media accountable!", "words": []}, {"post": "RT @WhiteHouse: President @realDonaldTrump and Prime Minister @AbeShinzo met for bilateral meetings and a working lunch at Akasaka Palace.…", "c_post": "RT @WhiteHouse: President @realDonaldTrump and Prime Minister @AbeShinzo met for bilateral meetings and a working lunch at Akasaka Palace.…", "words": [{"LOCATION": "Akasaka"}, {"LOCATION": "Palace.…"}]}, {"post": "RT @usembassytokyo: トランプ大統領とメラニア夫人は、天皇、皇后両陛下との会見に臨みました。@POTUS &amp; @FLOTUS were received by Their Majesties the Emperor and Empress of Japan.…", "c_post": "RT @usembassytokyo: トランプ大統領とメラニア夫人は、天皇、皇后両陛下との会見に臨みました。@POTUS and @FLOTUS were received by Their Majesties the Emperor and Empress of Japan.…", "words": []}, {"post": "Great evening last night, thank you! https://t.co/wPjj3yaaru", "c_post": "Great evening last night, thank you! ", "words": []}, {"post": "RT @usembassytokyo: トランプ大統領は安倍首相と共に皇居での歓迎式典に出席しました。@POTUS &amp; @AbeShinzo at the Imperial Palace for the Welcome Ceremony. #POTUSinJapan 🇺🇸🇯🇵…", "c_post": "RT @usembassytokyo: トランプ大統領は安倍首相と共に皇居での歓迎式典に出席しました。@POTUS and @AbeShinzo at the Imperial Palace for the Welcome Ceremony. #POTUSinJapan 🇺🇸🇯🇵…", "words": [{"ORGANIZATION": "Imperial"}, {"ORGANIZATION": "Palace"}]}, {"post": "Congratulations to the Great (and my friend) Roger Penske on winning his 18th (UNBELIEVABLE!) Indianapolis 500. I am in Japan, very early in the morning, but I got to watch Simon drive one of the greatest races in the history of the sport. I will see them both, &amp; TEAM, at the WH!", "c_post": "Congratulations to the Great (and my friend) Roger Penske on winning his 18th (UNBELIEVABLE!) Indianapolis 500. I am in Japan, very early in the morning, but I got to watch Simon drive one of the greatest races in the history of the sport. I will see them both, and TEAM, at the WH!", "words": [{"PERSON": "Roger"}, {"PERSON": "Penske"}, {"LOCATION": "Indianapolis"}, {"PERSON": "Simon"}]}, {"post": "The Great Patriots of Rolling Thunder WILL be coming back to Washington, D.C. next year, &amp; hopefully for many years to come. It is where they want to be, &amp; where they should be. Have a wonderful time today. Thank you to our great men &amp; women of the Pentagon for working it out!", "c_post": "The Great Patriots of Rolling Thunder WILL be coming back to Washington, D.C. next year, and hopefully for many years to come. It is where they want to be, and where they should be. Have a wonderful time today. Thank you to our great men and women of the Pentagon for working it out!", "words": [{"LOCATION": "Washington,"}, {"LOCATION": "D.C."}, {"ORGANIZATION": "Pentagon"}]}, {"post": "“Why doesn’t the press apologize to President Trump for the Russian Collusion Delusion?” @marklevinshow  @JudgeJeanine  How about the Dems also?", "c_post": "“Why doesn’t the press apologize to President Trump for the Russian Collusion Delusion?” @marklevinshow @JudgeJeanine How about the Dems also?", "words": [{"PERSON": "Trump"}]}, {"post": "Thank you @JPN_PMO @AbeShinzo! #POTUSinJapan🇺🇸🇯🇵 https://t.co/fWToB1XotG", "c_post": "Thank you @JPN_PMO @AbeShinzo! #POTUSinJapan🇺🇸🇯🇵 ", "words": []}, {"post": "Tonight in Tokyo, Japan at the Ryōgoku Kokugikan Stadium, it was my great honor to present the first-ever U.S. President’s Cup to Sumo Grand Champion Asanoyama. Congratulations! A great time had by all, thank you @AbeShinzo!! https://t.co/nwwxJl6KXH", "c_post": "Tonight in Tokyo, Japan at the Ryōgoku Kokugikan Stadium, it was my great honor to present the first-ever U.S. President’s Cup to Sumo Grand Champion Asanoyama. Congratulations! A great time had by all, thank you @AbeShinzo!! ", "words": [{"LOCATION": "Japan"}, {"LOCATION": "U.S."}]}, {"post": "Great progress being made in our Trade Negotiations with Japan. Agriculture and beef heavily in play. Much will wait until after their July elections where I anticipate big numbers!", "c_post": "Great progress being made in our Trade Negotiations with Japan. Agriculture and beef heavily in play. Much will wait until after their July elections where I anticipate big numbers!", "words": []}, {"post": "Great fun and meeting with Prime Minister @AbeShinzo. Numerous Japanese officials told me that the Democrats would rather see the United States fail than see me or the Republican Party succeed - Death Wish!", "c_post": "Great fun and meeting with Prime Minister @AbeShinzo. Numerous Japanese officials told me that the Democrats would rather see the United States fail than see me or the Republican Party succeed - Death Wish!", "words": [{"LOCATION": "United"}, {"LOCATION": "States"}, {"ORGANIZATION": "Republican"}, {"ORGANIZATION": "Party"}]}, {"post": "RT @AbeShinzo: 令和初の国賓としてお迎えしたトランプ大統領と千葉でゴルフです。新しい令和の時代も日米同盟をさらに揺るぎないものとしていきたいと考えています。 https://t.co/8ol8790xWY", "c_post": "RT @AbeShinzo: 令和初の国賓としてお迎えしたトランプ大統領と千葉でゴルフです。新しい令和の時代も日米同盟をさらに揺るぎないものとしていきたいと考えています。 ", "words": []}, {"post": "Great morning of golf with Prime Minister @AbeShinzo at Mobara Country Club in Chiba, Japan! https://t.co/EZeJ8znS51", "c_post": "Great morning of golf with Prime Minister @AbeShinzo at Mobara Country Club in Chiba, Japan! ", "words": [{"ORGANIZATION": "Mobara"}, {"ORGANIZATION": "Country"}, {"ORGANIZATION": "Club"}]}, {"post": "RT @USAmbJapan: Welcome back to Japan, Mr. President! @POTUS #POTUSinJapan #Alliance \nトランプ大統領、日本へようこそ！🇺🇸🇯🇵 https://t.co/kenxM9A7YF", "c_post": "RT @USAmbJapan: Welcome back to Japan, Mr. President! @POTUS #POTUSinJapan #Alliance トランプ大統領、日本へようこそ！🇺🇸🇯🇵 ", "words": []}, {"post": "North Korea fired off some small weapons, which disturbed some of my people, and others, but not me. I have confidence that Chairman Kim will keep his promise to me, &amp; also smiled when he called Swampman Joe Biden a low IQ individual, &amp; worse. Perhaps that’s sending me a signal?", "c_post": "North Korea fired off some small weapons, which disturbed some of my people, and others, but not me. I have confidence that Chairman Kim will keep his promise to me, and also smiled when he called Swampman Joe Biden a low IQ individual, and worse. Perhaps that’s sending me a signal?", "words": [{"LOCATION": "North"}, {"LOCATION": "Korea"}, {"PERSON": "Kim"}, {"PERSON": "Swampman"}, {"PERSON": "Joe"}, {"PERSON": "Biden"}]}, {"post": "Going to play golf right now with @AbeShinzo. Japan loves the game. Tremendous fans of @JackNicklaus, @TigerWoods, and @PhilMickelson — I said what about @GaryPlayer, they said we love Gary too!", "c_post": "Going to play golf right now with @AbeShinzo. Japan loves the game. Tremendous fans of @JackNicklaus, @TigerWoods, and @PhilMickelson — I said what about @GaryPlayer, they said we love Gary too!", "words": [{"LOCATION": "Japan"}, {"PERSON": "Gary"}, {"PERSON": "too!"}]}, {"post": "RT @AbeShinzo: President Trump and the First Lady are staying in Japan as the first State Guests of the new era “Reiwa”! TOKYO SKYTREE welc…", "c_post": "RT @AbeShinzo: President Trump and the First Lady are staying in Japan as the first State Guests of the new era “Reiwa”! TOKYO SKYTREE welc…", "words": [{"PERSON": "Trump"}, {"LOCATION": "Japan"}, {"LOCATION": "TOKYO"}]}, {"post": "RT @USAmbJapan: .@POTUS kicks off historic state visit by discussing ways to deepen economic ties with business leaders. #POTUSinJapan #All…", "c_post": "RT @USAmbJapan: .@POTUS kicks off historic state visit by discussing ways to deepen economic ties with business leaders. #POTUSinJapan #All…", "words": []}, {"post": "RT @GOPChairwoman: The @realDonaldTrump administration's fight for better trade deals doesn't end with China. \n\nThe president is working ha…", "c_post": "RT @GOPChairwoman: The @realDonaldTrump administration's fight for better trade deals doesn't end with China. The president is working ha…", "words": []}, {"post": "In addition to great incompetence and corruption, The Smollett case in Chicago is also about a Hate Crime. Remember, “MAGA COUNTRY DID IT!” That turned out to be a total lie, had nothing to do with “MAGA COUNTRY.” Serious stuff, and not even an apology to millions of people!", "c_post": "In addition to great incompetence and corruption, The Smollett case in Chicago is also about a Hate Crime. Remember, “MAGA COUNTRY DID IT!” That turned out to be a total lie, had nothing to do with “MAGA COUNTRY.” Serious stuff, and not even an apology to millions of people!", "words": [{"PERSON": "Smollett"}, {"LOCATION": "Chicago"}]}, {"post": "RT @TeamTrump: Dems plan a government TAKEOVER of healthcare.\n\nThat means ELIMINATING private plans (like Blue Cross/Blue Shield)! \n\n@reald…", "c_post": "RT @TeamTrump: Dems plan a government TAKEOVER of healthcare. That means ELIMINATING private plans (like Blue Cross/Blue Shield)! @reald…", "words": []}, {"post": "RT @JesseBWatters: TOMORROW: Senator @LindseyGrahamSC splashes into @WattersWorld to discuss his relationship with President @realDonaldTru…", "c_post": "RT @JesseBWatters: TOMORROW: Senator @LindseyGrahamSC splashes into @WattersWorld to discuss his relationship with President @realDonaldTru…", "words": []}, {"post": "RT @GOPChairwoman: Democrats and the mainstream media loved to talk about transparency until they learned @realDonaldTrump was declassifyin…", "c_post": "RT @GOPChairwoman: Democrats and the mainstream media loved to talk about transparency until they learned @realDonaldTrump was declassifyin…", "words": []}, {"post": "RT @jonvoight: To my fellow Americans. Part 2. https://t.co/uhqpbzwHhS", "c_post": "RT @jonvoight: To my fellow Americans. Part 2. ", "words": []}, {"post": "Thank you John, so nice! https://t.co/cfcXpzjYn7", "c_post": "Thank you John, so nice! ", "words": []}, {"post": "Another activist Obama appointed judge has just ruled against us on a section of the Southern Wall that is already under construction. This is a ruling against Border Security and in favor of crime, drugs and human trafficking. We are asking for an expedited appeal!", "c_post": "Another activist Otter appointed judge has just ruled against us on a section of the Southern Wall that is already under construction. This is a ruling against Border Security and in favor of crime, drugs and human trafficking. We are asking for an expedited appeal!", "words": [{"PERSON": "Obama"}, {"LOCATION": "Southern"}, {"LOCATION": "Wall"}, {"ORGANIZATION": "Border"}, {"ORGANIZATION": "Security"}]}, {"post": "RT @WhiteHouse: After arriving in Tokyo, President @realDonaldTrump spoke with Japanese business leaders at the U. S. Ambassador to Japan’s…", "c_post": "RT @WhiteHouse: After arriving in Tokyo, President @realDonaldTrump spoke with Japanese business leaders at the U. S. Ambassador to Japan’s…", "words": [{"LOCATION": "U."}, {"LOCATION": "S."}]}, {"post": "Getting ready to land in Japan with First Lady Melania. We look forward to seeing everyone soon!🇺🇸🇯🇵", "c_post": "Getting ready to land in Japan with First Lady Mackeral. We look forward to seeing everyone soon!🇺🇸🇯🇵", "words": [{"LOCATION": "Japan"}]}, {"post": "Can’t believe that Rolling Thunder would be given a hard time with permits in Washington, D.C. They are great Patriots who I have gotten to know and see in action. They love our Country and love our Flag. If I can help, I will!", "c_post": "Can’t believe that Rolling Thunder would be given a hard time with permits in Washington, D.C. They are great Patriots who I have gotten to know and see in action. They love our Country and love our Flag. If I can help, I will!", "words": []}, {"post": "Democrat Senator Mark Warner is acting and talking like he is in total control of the Senate Intelligence Committee. Their is nothing bipartisan about him. He should not be allowed to take “command” of that Committee. Too important! Remember when he spoke to the Russian jokester?", "c_post": "Democrat Senator Mark Warner is acting and talking like he is in total control of the Senate Intelligence Committee. Their is nothing bipartisan about him. He should not be allowed to take “command” of that Committee. Too important! Remember when he spoke to the Russian jokester?", "words": [{"PERSON": "Mark"}, {"PERSON": "Warner"}, {"ORGANIZATION": "Senate"}, {"ORGANIZATION": "Intelligence"}, {"ORGANIZATION": "Committee."}]}, {"post": "RT @Jim_Jordan: \"Rep. Jordan: When your focus is attacking Trump, you can't do what's best for America\"\n\nhttps://t.co/prJJfetQel", "c_post": "RT @Jim_Jordan: \"Rep. Jordan: When your focus is attacking Trump, you can't do what's best for America\" ", "words": []}, {"post": "The real trade war began 30 years ago, and we lost. This is a bright new Age, the Age of Enlightenment. We don’t lose anymore! https://t.co/5ECmBpsI6D", "c_post": "The real trade war began 30 years ago, and we lost. This is a bright new Age, the Age of Enlightenment. We don’t lose anymore! ", "words": []}, {"post": "RT @Jim_Jordan: We could work together on the big problems facing America.\n\nWe could solve the border crisis, lower the cost of prescriptio…", "c_post": "RT @Jim_Jordan: We could work together on the big problems facing America. We could solve the border crisis, lower the cost of prescriptio…", "words": []}, {"post": "RT @Jim_Jordan: Democrats are engaged in presidential obstruction. They're so desperate to stop the President that they won't help the coun…", "c_post": "RT @Jim_Jordan: Democrats are engaged in presidential obstruction. They're so desperate to stop the President that they won't help the coun…", "words": []}, {"post": "In Alaska with our GREAT TROOPS, departing shortly for Japan! https://t.co/9a72TMftpN", "c_post": "In Alaska with our GREAT TROOPS, departing shortly for Japan! ", "words": [{"LOCATION": "Alaska"}]}, {"post": ".....The Dems want a second shot at Bob Mueller, are very unhappy with the No Collusion Report. They should not be allowed to play this game any longer - no second chances - must get back to work. So bad for our Country!", "c_post": ".....The Dems want a second shot at Bob Mueller, are very unhappy with the No Collusion Report. They should not be allowed to play this game any longer - no second chances - must get back to work. So bad for our Country!", "words": [{"PERSON": "Bob"}, {"PERSON": "Mueller,"}]}, {"post": "....(with many more to come) and 2 Supreme Court Justices - we are getting into record territory! Thank you all and have a great Memorial Day Weekend.", "c_post": "....(with many more to come) and 2 Supreme Court Justices - we are getting into record territory! Thank you all and have a great Memorial Day Weekend.", "words": [{"ORGANIZATION": "Supreme"}, {"ORGANIZATION": "Court"}]}, {"post": "Mitch McConnell and our Republican Senators have been very solid and strong. We have accomplished a great deal together, in particular with our Courts, 107 Federal Judges....", "c_post": "Mitch McConnell and our Republican Senators have been very solid and strong. We have accomplished a great deal together, in particular with our Courts, 107 Federal Judges....", "words": [{"PERSON": "Mitch"}, {"PERSON": "McConnell"}]}, {"post": "https://t.co/8GRaqVxR8S", "c_post": "", "words": []}, {"post": "Departed the @WhiteHouse and am now on Air Force One with the First Lady heading to Japan and looking forward to honoring, on behalf of the United States, His Majesty, the Emperor of Japan. I will also be discussing Trade and Military with my friend, Prime Minister @AbeShinzo. https://t.co/uwEjQNbEXE", "c_post": "Departed the @WhiteHouse and am now on Air Force One with the First Lady heading to Japan and looking forward to honoring, on behalf of the United States, His Majesty, the Emperor of Japan. I will also be discussing Trade and Military with my friend, Prime Minister @AbeShinzo. ", "words": [{"LOCATION": "Japan"}, {"ORGANIZATION": "United"}]}, {"post": "Just spoke to Prime Minister @NarendraModi where I congratulated him on his big political victory. He is a great man and leader for the people of India - they are lucky to have him!", "c_post": "Just spoke to Prime Minister @NarendraModi where I congratulated him on his big political victory. He is a great man and leader for the people of India - they are lucky to have him!", "words": [{"LOCATION": "India"}]}, {"post": "Congratulations to Tom Cotton - his book, “Sacred Duty: A Solider’s Tour at Arlington National Cemetery” just hit the best sellers list. I was at @ArlingtonNatl yesterday &amp; the people there were so grateful for Tom’s inspiring portrait of “The Old Guard.” Great job @TomCottonAR!", "c_post": "Congratulations to Tom Cotton - his book, “Sacred Duty: A Solider’s Tour at Arlington National Cemetery” just hit the best sellers list. I was at @ArlingtonNatl yesterday and the people there were so grateful for Tom’s inspiring portrait of “The Old Guard.” Great job @TomCottonAR!", "words": [{"PERSON": "Tom"}, {"PERSON": "Cotton"}, {"LOCATION": "Arlington"}]}, {"post": "I don’t know why the Radical Left Democrats want Bob Mueller to testify when he just issued a 40 Million Dollar Report that states, loud &amp; clear &amp; for all to hear, No Collusion and No Obstruction (how do you Obstruct a NO crime?) Dems are just looking for trouble and a Do-Over!", "c_post": "I don’t know why the Radical Left Democrats want Bob Mueller to testify when he just issued a 40 Million Dollar Report that states, loud and clear and for all to hear, No Collusion and No Obstruction (how do you Obstruct a NO crime?) Dems are just looking for trouble and a Do-Over!", "words": [{"PERSON": "Bob"}, {"PERSON": "Mueller"}]}, {"post": "“If they try to Impeach President Trump, who has done nothing wrong (No Collusion), they will end up getting him re-elected” @LindseyGrahamSC Impeachment is for High Crimes and Misdemeanors. There were no High Crimes and Misdemeanors, except for those committed by the other side!", "c_post": "“If they try to Impeach President Trump, who has done nothing wrong (No Collusion), they will end up getting him re-elected” @LindseyGrahamSC Impeachment is for High Crimes and Misdemeanors. There were no High Crimes and Misdemeanors, except for those committed by the other side!", "words": []}, {"post": "“Intelligence Agencies were used against an American President.” @DevinNunes  @ShannonBream @FoxNews  This should NEVER happen to a President again! Dems are furious at Robert Mueller for his findings - NO COLLUSION, NO OBSTRUCTION. Now they should go back to work and legislate!", "c_post": "“Intelligence Agencies were used against an American President.” @DevinNunes @ShannonBream @FoxNews This should NEVER happen to a President again! Dems are furious at Robert Mueller for his findings - NO COLLUSION, NO OBSTRUCTION. Now they should go back to work and legislate!", "words": [{"PERSON": "Robert"}, {"PERSON": "Mueller"}]}, {"post": "When is Twitter going to allow the very popular Conservative Voices that it has so viciously shut down, back into the OPEN? IT IS TIME!", "c_post": "When is Twitter going to allow the very popular Conservative Voices that it has so viciously shut down, back into the OPEN? IT IS TIME!", "words": []}, {"post": "Wow! CNN Ratings are WAY DOWN, record lows. People are getting tired of so many Fake Stories and Anti-Trump lies. Chris Cuomo was rewarded for lowest morning ratings with a prime time spot - which is failing badly and not helping the dumbest man on television, Don Lemon!", "c_post": "Wow! CNN Ratings are WAY DOWN, record lows. People are getting tired of so many Fake Stories and Anti-Trump lies. Chris Cuomo was rewarded for lowest morning ratings with a prime time spot - which is failing badly and not helping the dumbest man on television, Don Lemon!", "words": [{"PERSON": "Chris"}, {"PERSON": "Cuomo"}]}, {"post": "RT @HeyTammyBruce: Very excited to join the @foxnation team! “Fox Nation Rolls Out Slate With Tyrus, Kat Timpf, Tammy Bruce, Lawrence Jones…", "c_post": "RT @HeyTammyBruce: Very excited to join the @foxnation team! “Fox Nation Rolls Out Slate With Tyrus, Kat Timpf, Tammy Bruce, Lawrence Jones…", "words": [{"PERSON": "Tammy"}, {"PERSON": "Bruce,"}, {"PERSON": "Lawrence"}, {"PERSON": "Jones…"}]}, {"post": "RT @NikkiHaley: A great night. Thank you. ❤️ https://t.co/EIKFo2UMLy", "c_post": "RT @NikkiHaley: A great night. Thank you. ❤️ ", "words": []}, {"post": "RT @TPUSA: SPEAKER ANNOUNCEMENT!\n\nFox News Contributor @LisaMarieBooth Has Just Been Added To Our AMAZING Line-Up Of Speakers For #YWLS2019…", "c_post": "RT @TPUSA: SPEAKER ANNOUNCEMENT! Fox News Contributor @LisaMarieBooth Has Just Been Added To Our AMAZING Line-Up Of Speakers For #YWLS2019…", "words": []}, {"post": "RT @TomFitton: BIG: @realDonaldTrump authorizes AG Barr to declassify #Spygate docs from all agencies!  Coming up! https://t.co/PzzU0kNQfL", "c_post": "RT @TomFitton: BIG: @realDonaldTrump authorizes AG Barr to declassify #Spygate docs from all agencies! Coming up! ", "words": [{"ORGANIZATION": "AG"}, {"ORGANIZATION": "Barr"}]}, {"post": "RT @TomFitton: FBI refuses to search text messages under FOIA. Director Wray needs to step up and stop this stonewalling that protects corr…", "c_post": "RT @TomFitton: FBI refuses to search text messages under FOIA. Director Wray needs to step up and stop this stonewalling that protects corr…", "words": [{"ORGANIZATION": "FBI"}, {"PERSON": "Wray"}]}, {"post": "71% of Voters rate the Economy as Excellent or Good. The highest number in more than 18 years! @QuinnipiacPoll", "c_post": "71% of Voters rate the Economy as Excellent or Good. The highest number in more than 18 years! @QuinnipiacPoll", "words": []}, {"post": "RT @DonaldJTrumpJr: A friendly reminder from @LizRNC that the Main Stream Media who suffer from Trump Detangment Syndrome made this clown a…", "c_post": "RT @DonaldJTrumpJr: A friendly reminder from @LizRNC that the Main Stream Media who suffer from Trump Detangment Syndrome made this clown a…", "words": []}, {"post": "“PELOSI STAMMERS THROUGH NEWS CONFERENCE” https://t.co/1OyCyqRTuk", "c_post": "“PELOSI STAMMERS THROUGH NEWS CONFERENCE” ", "words": []}, {"post": "RT @AviBerkow: Congrats ⁦@IvankaTrump⁩ on receiving the Internet Association’s 2019 Internet Freedom Award this evening. https://t.co/dE6Zh…", "c_post": "RT @AviBerkow: Congrats ⁦@IvankaTrump⁩ on receiving the Internet Association’s 2019 Internet Freedom Award this evening. …", "words": []}, {"post": "“Nancy Pelosi should not be out there doing the kinds of things she is doing. She will diminish herself and her membership. She cannot put a subject with a predicate in the same sentence. What’s going on?”  Ed Rollins  @GreggJarrett  @LouDobbs", "c_post": "“Nancy Pelosi should not be out there doing the kinds of things she is doing. She will diminish herself and her membership. She cannot put a subject with a predicate in the same sentence. What’s going on?” Ed Rollins @GreggJarrett @LouDobbs", "words": [{"PERSON": "Pelosi"}, {"PERSON": "Ed"}, {"PERSON": "Rollins"}]}, {"post": "....Today’s action will help ensure that all Americans learn the truth about the events that occurred, and the actions that were taken, during the last Presidential election and will restore confidence in our public institutions.” @PressSec", "c_post": "....Today’s action will help ensure that all Americans learn the truth about the events that occurred, and the actions that were taken, during the last Presidential election and will restore confidence in our public institutions.” @PressSec", "words": []}, {"post": "....during the 2016 Presidential election. The Attorney General has also been delegated full and complete authority to declassify information pertaining to this investigation, in accordance with the long-established standards for handling classified information....", "c_post": "....during the 2016 Presidential election. The Attorney General has also been delegated full and complete authority to declassify information pertaining to this investigation, in accordance with the long-established standards for handling classified information....", "words": []}, {"post": "“Today, at the request and recommendation of the Attorney General of the United States, President Donald J. Trump directed the intelligence community to quickly and fully cooperate with the Attorney General’s investigation into surveillance activities....", "c_post": "“Today, at the request and recommendation of the Attorney General of the United States, President Donald J. Trump directed the intelligence community to quickly and fully cooperate with the Attorney General’s investigation into surveillance activities....", "words": [{"ORGANIZATION": "United"}, {"PERSON": "Donald"}, {"PERSON": "J."}, {"PERSON": "Trump"}]}, {"post": "@FoxNews Poll: A majority of Americans want the Democrats to stop investigating President Trump. The Mueller Report said very strongly NO COLLUSION, which led to NO OBSTRUCTION. The Dems can’t get over 2016 or the conclusive Mueller findings. They are now the Do Nothing Party!", "c_post": "@FoxNews Poll: A majority of Americans want the Democrats to stop investigating President Trump. The Mueller Report said very strongly NO COLLUSION, which led to NO OBSTRUCTION. The Dems can’t get over 2016 or the conclusive Mueller findings. They are now the Do Nothing Party!", "words": [{"PERSON": "Mueller"}]}, {"post": "The U.S. Senate has just approved a 19 Billion Dollar Disaster Relief Bill, with my total approval. Great!", "c_post": "The U.S. Senate has just approved a 19 Billion Dollar Disaster Relief Bill, with my total approval. Great!", "words": [{"ORGANIZATION": "U.S."}, {"ORGANIZATION": "Senate"}]}]